Olesia Pryhun

Junior front-end developer

PORTFOLIO

My detailed portfolio with pet projects: https://portfolio- pryhun.netlify.app/.

My GitHub account: https://github.com/Olesia-P.

ABOUT ME

I completed a front-end course, then spent some time studying with the help of an experienced web developer and on my own.

I constantly improve my skills and continue writing pet projects. I use a variety of tools to learn, including documentation, forums, YouTube, and ChatGPT.

MongoDB

Next.js API

SKILLS

Front-end:

Back-end

- TypeScript
- Next.js
- React
- Redux
- Sass/Scss
- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML

- Git + Bash
- GraphQL

Other

- Postman



- pryhun.o@gmail.com
- Telegram: @Pryhun Olesia
- <u>LinkedIn</u>
- **=** +380681250102

LOCATION

- Ukraine, Kyiv
- Or remote work

LANGUAGE

- English C1 (CAE Certificate), advanced
- Ukrainian (native)

EDUCATION

Online front-end course (SheCodes)

2023

Online QA Manual course (Hillel)

2022

Kyiv National Linguistic University

Bachelor of Language and Literature (Japanese)

2015 - 2019

HOBBIES

- Jigsaw puzzles
- Coloring books
- Board games

EXPERIENCE

Practicing web development

2023-2024

2019-2023

English Teacher

Language courses

• I taught teenagers and adults English, individually and in groups, offline and online.